Yes, it's almost like a fixture at NAB, though the songs are, well, they're like subs for the announcer, in other words, they're all you can use.
Now, one of our idols who often comes to NPB is this lady, hello ladies and gentlemen, we're here to grab your crowns!
We are Crown Pop, and we're here to grab your crown!
We're here to get your crown, and we're going to say, "We're Crown Pop.
When you say hello to someone, you say, "Hi, I'm Crown Pop.
This is a very important point.
In the video I made the day before the Staples Festival...
We talked about this in the video I uploaded the day before this year's StarPlaza festival.
Yes, sir.
You know...
About the Stapler Fest...
Did you talk about the Stapler Fest with everyone at Crown Pop?
Yes, we did.
It's not so much about the StarPlaza festival.
It's more about the color of our future clampo...
It's not about "StarPlaza festival".
We talked about it as a group.
So the timing was just right.
Yes, it was.
What did you talk about at the Klampo meeting?
Yes, that's right.
We really talked about it in the video.
But I've already told you almost everything.
But it's not a catchphrase or anything.
I'd like to talk about how we're going to go from now on and what we're going to show in the future.
What do we want to show in the future, or what is missing?
We have a wide range of music.
But I wonder if that wide range of music is causing us to lose some of our color.
We talk about whether or not we are losing some of our color by having such a wide range of music.
Who started that?
Well, it's not so much who started it.
It's just that of all the gigs we've done
There was a time when our recent live show was really shabby.
That's when we started talking about it.
I told Mr. Mita that he was great a few times when I saw him live.
He said, "No, not yet.
I've hardly ever heard anything else from him.
Isn't that too harsh?
It's a very high level of performance.
Thank you very much.
I've seen a lot of idols.
I've seen a lot of idols, and I'm sure we're not done yet.
We have to do our best.
Of course, we've been told we're cute.
and that we are good dancers.
But of course, there are other things.
But if you were to ask me what I mean when I say "Clambop"...
I can't answer anything.
Then I say, "Dancing.
To be honest, there are other groups that can dance better.
There are more groups that can dance like this.
With a tilt of the head
And they say, "No, no, no, there's a group that can dance better.
I say, "No, there aren't.
That's exactly what I'm saying.
Korean idols are coming and coming and coming.
There are some who can dance and sing in unison
And some of them are doing very well.
Of course, they do it in different ways.
I'm proud to say that we have been dancing for a long time.
We have been dancing for a long time.
If you ask us if we can say that we sell dance
To be honest, we don't have it all together.
A little bit of a different choreography here and there.
or the right part is a little to the left out of habit.
or the part where we stretch is bent.
There are a lot of small details.
It may look like that to the people around you...
Some of the staff members pointed this out to me.
I've had a lot of comments from the staff.
I guess you could say that.
I think we have to do something by ourselves.
And the timing of this Yokohama Arena was almost the same or close to the same.
Was the timing of the Yokohama Arena close to the same time?
Well, we didn't have a lecture originally.
But we have been having meetings and discussions every year, like in 2021 or 2022.
We have been discussing the year 2021 or 2022 every year, and we all agreed that Yokohama Arena was a good idea.
Well, I wanted to say it properly at the concert.
But to be honest, we haven't been able to do a live show where we could say that we've done our best.
We couldn't say what we were going to say at the show, and even though we said we'd say it at the next show
And then we couldn't say what we were going to say at the next show because we felt it wasn't good enough, and so we couldn't say it.
I felt like that wasn't good enough, and I couldn't say anything, and I felt like that wasn't good enough either.
I had to say something before, like, "Well, Grabo-chan, where are you aiming for?
So that's why we decided to hold the Staples Festival at Yokohama Arena.
So you're thinking of Yokohama Arena for the Staples Festival?
So, the only places where you can actually go to Yokohama Arena are places like Staples Festival and Elleraselle.
So I thought it would be meaningful to take pictures there.
So I made a public announcement that I was going to Yokohama Arena.
And you also changed your greeting.
We've been doing this for years.
You changed the familiar greeting.
And he went for your crown.
I'm sorry, but it's almost like they're all royalty.
I've never seen a child walking down the street wearing a crown.
He went to get it for you.
Of course I'm not wearing it.
It's in my heart.
I'm sorry.
Do you all have a crown on your heart?
We all do.
People who like idols...People who like idols
have a favorite idol or a favorite group, etc.
for that person.
Then, the most
For example, let's say it's a crown.
That's what we're going to do
We grab it.
Your
Ushida-san's best group
so that people will say "Crapo!
to say that Crapo is the best group
Originally, we were going to grab the crown of the entertainment industry
to aim high in the world of show business
to reach a higher level.
But of course
That's fine, but...
But then...
What is the crown of show business for each member
What is the crown of show business for each member?
I think everyone should be like this
As long as you're an idol
You want to make people smile.
For that person
Crapo is a way of life
To make people's lives worth living
That's what we all want to do.
That's why we are a group.
That's the meaning of the group.
So...
I don't know if it's just a catchphrase
It's a catchphrase.
Of course
I still want to win the crown in the entertainment industry, but
but there is also a feeling
I think it's a little bit different from what we really want.
With the catchphrases we've used so far, we're talking about ourselves.
This time it's about the fans.
That's why we changed the catchphrase, because we thought it was a little different.
So, I hope that's the way it's going to be.
It's not all Crapo fans anymore, you know.
Now there are fans from all the different groups, and we've changed what we're going to do and even changed the greeting.
The first thing they'll think is, "Crapo has changed.
It was very important what we were going to do.
Did you think it up by yourselves from Setori?
No, it wasn't just us.
Of course we included our opinions, but we also listened to the opinions of the staff.
Of course, we included our opinions, but we also listened to the staff's opinions as well.
But we had only 12 minutes for the competition.
We had 11 groups each, and there were a lot of competitions.
So we had to decide how many songs to play in the 12 minutes.
We were asked to choose how many songs we would play in the 12 minutes.
but most of the songs were around 5 minutes long.
But most of our songs are around 5 minutes long.
If we did three songs, it would be too long.
So we decided to do two songs.
Those two songs are very meaningful.
Then we started discussing if everyone else was going to do 3 songs and 2 songs
We started discussing and deciding whether we would play one song if everyone else was going to play three or two.
The live parts were "Bamboo Shoot Gnocchi," "Natsu Kirari," and "Our Testimony.
I think "Bamboo Shoot Gnocchi" is something you've never done before.
We never played that kind of club pop before, right?
That's really true.
So when I heard the song
I thought it would be a lot of fun.
It was a big shock.
That's why it was even more so.
What's that? It's a new kind of club pop.
What's that? I was a little surprised at first, but
I was a little surprised at first.
But now we've made it our own.
But we're running out of time.
It's a half version of the song, but it's in blue, the color of the club, and in red.
The color of the club is blue and the costume is red, so even if you see it for the first time, it's red and blue and the side yukata is red and blue.
I was so happy to see that the side yukata were already filled with red and blue.
And the day before, we were taking pictures of the yukata in the log of the arena, right?
And I really thought of you when I saw that.
I thought, "Mita-san, no matter how silly you usually are, you wouldn't do this.
What? You would?
No matter how silly it is, it's a song.
No, when it's not a song.
When it's not a song?
I think the person who can make that is the person who usually comes up with that kind of thing.
Oh, I see. Yes, that's right.
When you think of it as a song, you give it your all, don't you?
Yes, once I get into it, I don't think about it.
If I hadn't been an idol, there's a chance my life would have been smaller.
You don't think so, Ms. Mita?
Wow!
I know it sounds strange, but doing crazy things...
Do you think your life has expanded because you're an idol?
But on the contrary...
Before you became an idol, you were just like you are now.
But on the other hand, before I became an idol, I was just like I am now, and after I became an idol, I lost my character or something.
I don't think I would ever say that I would never do something like that.
If I wasn't an idol, I don't know if I would be an actress or a model.
If I wasn't an idol, I don't know if I would be an actress or a model, but I think I would be more conscious of various things, like being more careful with my language.
So now that you are an idol, what are you conscious of now?
What are you conscious of now that you are an idol?
I don't have an idea of what I should be like.
As an idol, I want to make people smile, so I think about that a lot.
You want to make people smile?Do you want to make people smile?
When do you make people smile?
When?
By their presence, or rather, just their presence.
I don't know how to say it.
Of course, singing and performance are part of it.
But if a person is there as a human being, if he/she is working hard somewhere...
Even if it's just to say that I'm doing something outside of the club.
Even if it is just saying that I am doing something outside of the club, it can be a source of energy for the people who are watching me.
Even if they just say, "I saw this..." or "I'm doing my best.
Even if they just say, "I saw this," I feel like I'm doing something good for people.
You are pushed, aren't you?
If you are pushed, you will be pushed, right?
I think you were able to show a different kind of cloud at the Obama Arena this time.
What do you think?
That was the first video we released, too.
Of course, we don't know what the right answer is.
To be honest, we didn't know until we tried it.
We also didn't know how much of a response we would get from the video.
Of course, not all of the people who came to Yokoyotsu may have seen the video.
That's one of the reasons.
Well, the most dancable bamboo shoot gnocchi
It's easy for everyone to imitate.
It's the newest song on the album, so I'd like you to play it.
I also wanted to mix it up.
But when we actually went out, almost everyone who came to Yokohama danced.
But when we actually went out, almost everyone who came to Yokohama
I didn't even think that most of the people who came to Yokohama had seen the video.
I don't think they even watched the video, but they imitated the person next to them and did the same thing.
I think it was a very meaningful experience.
Let's go back to the beginning.
The bamboo shoot gnocchi has a lot of Chiaki Mayumura in it, doesn't it?
That's right.
It's as if she made it for me.
So your boyfriend likes it now?
Yes, he does.
He likes it.
And you're not ashamed of it?
No, I'm not embarrassed.
I'm happy that everyone is enjoying it.
So how do you feel after Yokohama Arena?
Has the club changed?
I think it has changed.
Changed?
I don't mean on the surface.
I mean in our daily lessons and rehearsals.
I think we can now express our opinions
I think we're able to say what we think should be done.
We point out things to each other.
And we accept each other's opinions.
I think things have changed a lot.
What have you said recently? About the club's activities?
About the activities?
We've already had a meeting.
Is it such a big deal?
What?
I can't.
Is there a weapon in there somewhere that you'd like to see us use?
No, no, no, no, no, no.
But...
Yes, I do.
I mean, you know, for the future.
I do say that.
Mita-san is actually saying that.
But she says it calmly and weakly again.
I don't think it's possible that other people don't hear it.
I hope that's the case.
I hope so.
I think so.
The other members of the club are very cheerful.
That's right.
Who's the quietest of them all?
Maybe.
I'd like to hear what the other members have to say.
If that's the case...
I'd like to hear what the other members have to say about the group.
I'd like to share with those who are watching this
I'd be happy to hear your personal or Crapo story.
I'd like to ask you to give me one last word.
What should I do?
Let's see...
I don't know.
So that's how you feel.
What else would you have liked?
Did you want to promote your new movie?
No, no, no, no.
Yes, either about individuals or about groups.
Or both.
Yes.
Not so much individual?
Mmm-hmm.
Do you have any?
Oh, I don't. Oh, you do!
Well, do you want me to?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Actually, is there something you'd like to do if I gave you 200 million? Something like that.
No, no, no.
Yes, I would. Um.
Clanpop, I mentioned that we are aiming for Yokohama Arena.
But on December 28th of this year, we are going to perform at ZEPP Diver City.
We are going to have a solo live concert at ZEPP Diver City on December 28th this year.We will be doing a solo live show as a revenge.
Last time we performed at ZEPP.
Unfortunately, the venue was not filled.
So, we are very happy that we were able to do it this year.
This year, we want to make sure that we can deliver a satisfying live show to those who come to the venue.
I am sure that this year we will be able to satisfy those who came to the show.
I would like to make sure that those of you who have just seen us here will be satisfied with our live show.
I would like you to come to the show.
If you would like to join us, please let me know.
I hope you will be able to come on December 28th, even if it is just in the corner of your schedule.
Thank you very much.
So you are going to be brought up by Takenoko, is that right?
Takenoko?
I think that's going to catch on. At each site.
I think it will be a lot of fun when we play opposite each other.
We haven't had a pairing recently, so I'd love to go.
I'm looking forward to summer festivals.
Takenoko, which I could see well at the end of the year, will be there.
I would be happy if that is the case.
Can I talk about something personal?
A personal story...
I'll tell you something.
I really think this is...
I hope we can do radio together again.
Please let me be positive and get it.
I will do my best.
So, it was Kronpop Ebuki Mita who came this time.
Thank you very much.